VISETH KONG

Address: 1998 St.Lu5, Stueng Mean Chey, Phnom Penh, Tel: 087 856 327

Email: visethkong15@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/viseth-kong-3a9307159
My Portfolio Website: https://wisethkong.github.io/myportfolio/

Career Profile

Creative designer and frontend developer with solid problem-solving skills and hardworking graduate student from Bachelor of information technology with time management and teamwork skills developed through casual employment and volunteer work. Strong ability to implement mock-ups, and understanding of user experience design with proficiency in HTML, JavaScript, and CSS. A little experience with Java, C#, and .Net developed through my learning period in university.

Education

11/2021 – Current Master of Information Technology

Deakin University, Melbourne, Australia

Expected completion date: June 2023

Specializations: Software And Services Development

03/2019 – 07/2021 Bachelor of Information Technology

Deakin University, Melbourne, Australia

• Major: Application Development

03/2018 - 02/2019 Diploma of Computing

Deakin College, Melbourne, Australia

10/2012 – 07/2017 High School Diploma

American Intercon School, Phnom Penh, Cambodia

- School Sports Captain 2015 2017
- Member of the Volunteer Team 2017

Employment

04/2021 – Current Freelance UI/UX Designer

Part Time Job

- Created Interactive Prototypes, Low to High-Fidelity Wireframes
- Provided content strategy, UI design direction, and user experience design
- Designed UI for responsive websites and applications using Adobe XD,
 Photoshop, and Figma.

11/2020 - 12/2020

Android Developer Internship

VTI Corporation, Hanoi, Vietnam

- Worked from home environment, and developed an online banking application
- Environment Android Studio, Android SDK, IDE, Java, XML, Android Development Tools.
- Created new UI Activities and resources for layout UI work using XML, Shape Drawable, Text View, Buttons, Frame Layout.
- Involved in the project including development, debugging, testing and using Gitlab to develop and combine the project
- Connected application with Firebase real-time database

Additional Training

04/2019

Barista Certificate (Level 2)

The Espresso School, Clayton South

- Learned fundamental barista skills
- Learned how to pour latte art

10/2017 - 12/2017

Graphic design

Setec Institute, Phnom Penh, Cambodia

- Using Photoshop as a design tool
- Learned basic knowledge about UX design
- Designed name card, poster, brochure, and food menu

Volunteer Experience

03/2017-09/2017

Event Organiser Volunteer

The Luminous Night, Phnom Penh, Cambodia

- Created posters and ticket flyers, communicated with local news organisations
- Responsible for The Prom Night tickets and online promotion, including the creation of content on Facebook, and other various social media sites
- Provided friendly, timely support to customers both in-person and over the phone

11/2019

Graphic Designer & Photographer

Chapei Dong Veng Cultural Festival, Phnom Penh, Cambodia

- Created design ideas for both print and online platforms such as posters, backdrop, X-stand, and Facebook frame
- Maintained graphic files such as photos and logos.
- Photographer for the events and improvised photographic methods and techniques
- Used Photoshop and Lightroom to edit the photos
- Attended and contributed to team meetings

Extra-curricular Activities

04/2015 - 05/2017

Soccer Club Team Captain

Mengly J. Quach Soccer Championship, Phnom Penh, Cambodia

- Encouraged and supported team members by guiding on improving their skills
- provided leadership by setting a good example, both on and off the field
- Motivated team members by recognising their effort and contributions

References

Nguyen Vu Hung

Supervisor VTI Corporation

Email: hung.nguyenvu@vti.com.vn

Chutivet Khiev

Volunteer Team Leader The Luminous Night TEL: +855 96 316 6960

Email: Chutivetkh@gmail.com